throwing intercepted. [cheering]
Fitzpatrick
>> picked off by Ma Fitzpatrick. Ma
Fitzpatrick has it. The allproming
[music] up in Oldbridge, would you ever
dream that you wouldn't be here about 30
miles away playing for the Jets?
>> To be honest, no.
Not Not in a bad sense. But um you know,
I just I think it's just so surreal. You
know what I'm saying? I mean, I've I
played I' I've done high school [music]
competitions on this, you know, very
turf field. I played state championships
at Metife. Um, and I never thought, you
know, I would be back here competing
again, just at a much different
different level.
>> What were those experiences like? You're
on the field turf here, maybe inside or
you're outside just a couple steps away.
>> Yeah. And did you think that, hey, I got
a chance as far as playing in the
National Football League and I might be
playing
>> 10 seasons?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Um, I feel like just
naturally I'm I'm very like uh I don't
want to say I'm not farsighted, but I
like to be where my feet are. You know
what I'm saying? And you know, when I
was in high [music] school, like I I was
just think about the next step. You know
what I'm saying? Like I wanted to get to
to college and and play at a high level
in college. Then when I got to college,
I wanted to, you know, play at a high
level [music] in in the league. And um
so when I was when I was here, like I
was just worried about being here. You
know what I'm saying? I never thought
about uh uh if it was actually a
possibility to to to make the the next
step or actually uh I never thought
about, you know, wearing the the [music]
green and white. I
>> mean, I got to imagine that high school
is going to be jumping throughout the
fall now.
>> Yeah. I'm excited to be able to go go
Friday, watch some Friday night
football. Um, you know, uh, watch watch
those guys compete. You know, our um, a
lot of my old coaches are are still, you
know, coaching at that school or other
schools. So, it'll be fun [music] to
just, uh, you know, take a take a step
back into the the time portal and, uh,
watch some good high school football.
>> Yeah. So, let's bring it to present day.
What was your reaction when you found
out the deal was final that okay the
trade happens and this is going to be
your third team in three years now?
>> Yeah. Um you know it's it's a it's an
unfortunate part of you know the
business that that we do you know having
to move cities and whatnot and you know
of a young son and a young family. But
at the end of the day, uh, you know, I
[music] think what we do, um, and and
the things that we sacrifice are worth
it. And, uh, it makes us work even
harder cuz I don't want to move my son
to three different cities in 3 years,
uh, to [music] not produce a a good
result. You know what I'm saying? Um,
and
uh, you know, I was I was I was excited
to [music] uh, play for it for AG. you
know, he's a guy who played high level
football in the league [music] and now
he's coaching uh in the league and uh he
played defensive back, [music] you know,
same position as as myself. So, uh it's
exciting to be able to play for a guy
who has already done what what I've done
and and he he's gone through what what
I'm going through, you know what I'm
saying? And uh can relate to on on a lot
of different levels.
>> What's it like talking to him? because
[music]
him like yourself, former first round
pick and like you said, such an [music]
accomplished career, but can you feel
the energy come through when you jump on
the phone or you see him in the halls
here?
>> Because to a man, every person said
that,
>> you know, Aaron is a guy that he is a
natural leader [music] and he's a guy
who was intent on turning this culture
around. Yeah, [music] I think um I think
culture is is very big to him. Uh and
when you look at any good program,
whether that be a Fortune 500 company or
even a healthy household, I think
[music]
uh you know, it starts at the top. Uh it
starts with the leader setting the
standard. Uh it starts with the leader
>> [music]
>> um you know uh uh being the example uh
for everyone else. And I think AG AG
does that and he makes it easy. Uh when
the leader is doing the right thing and
he's challenging himself and he's
accepting um you [music] know counsel
from from other coaches and and and
other uh experienced people [music]
uh it makes it easy [clears throat] for
the players to to reflect that same that
same model. Um so I think it's it's
really crucial and really important
[music] uh to have that in the head
coach and I'm grateful that we have that
in AG. You're certainly not an old guy
by any means, but when you walk in that
locker room, you will be one of the
older players on a very young roster.
You are a multiple time Pro Bowler, you
are a multiple [music]
time all pro.
>> What are you going to bring to this team
as far as aside from the leadership,
aside from the intangibles, [music]
as far as make it the player?
>> Yeah. Um, I think uh I would I would
like to bring
uh
passion to the field that's that's
contagious. All great defenses have a
secondary that is physical. [music] They
play with an attitude or a chip on their
on their shoulder. Um they're
disciplined. They aren't making many
mistakes. Um when other teams are are
scouting us and and and and planning for
us, uh they're not we're not going to be
predictable. Uh, but we're also not
going to be chaotic. You know what I'm
saying? We're going to have a a rhyme
and a reason uh to to why we do things,
why I do things, why [music] I play
things certain way. Um,
yeah. So, that's that's what I think.
And the great thing about you [music] is
you're a weapon. Sometimes people say
you can go positionless on defense and
you're a guy can be used all throughout
the secondary. Bill. [music] Uh, we
can't wait to see where they're going to
be lining you up on Sundays. Yes, sir.
>> Throughout the fall.
>> Welcome back.
>> Yes, sir. Thank you. Appreciate you.